

Vitalii Bondarchuk

Junior Front-end & React JS Developer

- +38 096 266 90 70
- S vit.bondarchuk
- @ vit.bondarchuk@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/vitalii-bondarchuk/
- Yviv, Ukraine

SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer with multitasking skills. More than 5 years of working experience in IT as a UI/UX & graphic designer. Attentive to details. Supportive and enthusiastic team player for streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues in the future team. Friendly, positive, highly motivated person.

SKILLS

HTML5 JavaScript UI / UX CSS3 React JS Figma SCSS / Sass Redux Sketch Git / GitHub NPM / Yarn Photoshop Webpack AJAX Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Front-end & UI/UX 12/2018 - present time

- coding parts of sites in JavaScript: modal windows, API requests, sorting data, visual effects etc.;
- coding in React.is:
- layouting using approved mockups: HTML/CSS, preprocessors;
- verifying and modifying UI designs.

Luxoft, IT Company

UI/UX & Graphic Designer 07/2015 - 11/2018

- support designs for Luxoft's products;
- presentations/banners/prints;
- making video tutorials for software.

FCB, Advertising Agency

DTP-Designer

- working with whole range of prints;
- color correction and profiling;
- 03/2008 06/2015 3D-molding, stereo-vario.

GITHUB & DESIGN PORTFOLIO

- https://github.com/vitbon
- Be https://www.behance.net/vitbon

LANGUAGES

English intermediate





EDUCATION

Cursor Education

Advanced Front-end Course 07/2020 - 10/2020

- HTML5 / CSS3:
- JavaScript (ES5 / ES6+);
- React JS.

Vinnitsa Technical University

Faculty of Computer Systems 09/1996 - 06/2001

- C, Basic, Assembler coding;
- programming measuring devices;
- honors degree.

Kyiv Evangel University

Faculty of Christian Education 09/2014 - 08/2018

• branch of Global University (USA);

- modern western programm;
- American lecturers.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cursor Education

Advanced Front-end 07/2020 - 10/2020

- modern technologies;
- many practical tasks;
- excellent final result.

Luxoft, IT Company

English Courses 10/2016 - 10/2018

- British programm;
 - upper intermediate level;
 - native speaker.

INTERESTS









POST SCRIPTUM

Does your company need a proactive specialist with a desire to develop and move your business forward? Contact me, I'm that person! ©

Design Photo/Video

Literature

History